

## **STATEMENT**

I am a product designer with very refined taste and absolute care for detail. I am curious to learn about the users and have empathy on their pain points. And I take great pride in my ability to think outside the box, and my attention to details has always generated successful results of an improved user experience.

## **EXPERIENCES**

03/2018 - Present Product Designer

@ Jyve

Focused on digital products design for ios app, android app and dashboard

 @ Pillow

Performed as a leading designer for marketing lunch including ad banners, brochures, door hangers, email campaigns, powerpoint presentations, iconography, and landing pages

Worked with Engineer and Marketing team to design interaction and user interface for dashboard and responsive websites following a systematic process Collected and analyzed user behavior through user testing and came up with design strategy under brand guideline

05/2016 - 01/2017 Web

Web Designer & Developer

@ VolunteerMatch

Worked with Client Service & Support team to strategize and build new help center website through sitemaps, wireframes

Developed Help Center websites in Zendesk utilizing HTML CSS Javascript and template language

10/2015 - 12/2015

**UI/UX** Designer

@ KidzJet

Developed pixel-perfect wireframe and mock-ups for KidzJet web-based dashboard and mobile application for both passenger and driver Participated in all phases of the product development lifecycle from ideation

and definition, to interface design, user research and testing

06/2015 - 10/2015

**UI/UX Designer** 

@ Hubtag Inc.

Designed pixel-perfect mockups for Hubtag live streaming software dashboard, and enhanced users experience by providing new responsive website layout

SKILLS

Sketch HTML User Research CSS Adobe Photoshop Interactive Design Adobe Illustrator Sass **Animation Creation** Adobe Premiere Javascript Speed Wireframing Adobe After Effect jQuery Concept Development Adobe Indesign Marketo Font-end Development

## **EDUCATION**

09/2016 - 05/2018 Academy of Art University

Master of Art in Web Design & New Media

09/2013 - 06/2015 University of Washington, Information School

Master of Science in Library and Information Science

08/2009 - 06/2013

Shanghai University, Department of Library and Archives

Bachelor of Arts in Library and Archives

(206) 953 0326 qianqiandesign@gmail.com qianqianwangdesign.com